now and I think
it's pretty absurd I'm
show this to you
is that if individuals
are earning money now
and they're using Buy
Pay Later to buy
things online and then
they're it on not
very productive things It's
not like they're buying
maybe you buy a
MacBook and you do
podcasts with your MacBook
and you make money
with that that's great
That's productive spending It's
like la boos and
it nailed it So
there's a of like
non productive spending So
I'll use like a
say on TikTok shop
right So I spoke
to a lot of
people who are involved
in that ecosystem and
saying that okay what
are people buying And
then a of it
are not actually productive
stuff They're like perfumes
or they're like and
so there's just like
stuff you don't actually
need So they don't
fully make you they
don't influence your Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah The
ROI is not great
The ROI is not
great That is terrible
right It's Yeah it's
terrible right So what
has Buy Pay Later
done And what has
like what has credit
cards you done for
the S back then
You and so I
think they inject a
lot of they help
the because they loss
spending Yeah So